The Stranger in My Home is a thriller, drama film directed by Jeff Fisher.
A handsome stranger's claim that a couple's 15-year-old daughter was switched at birth
throws their perfect family into turmoil, unearthing shattering secrets.
Ali, played by Sophia Bush.
Tom Truby, played by Chris Carmack.
Detective Miriam Davis, played by Briana Price.
Katie Mitchell, played by Amiah Miller.
Sam, played by Kate Rachesky.
Sarah, played by Monica Lacy.
Die My Love is a 2025 American psychological drama film directed by Lynne
Ramsay, who co-wrote the screenplay with Enda Walsh and Alice Birch.
Based on the 2012 novel by Ariana Harwicz, it follows a young mother (Jennifer Lawrence) in rural Montana whose severe
postpartum depression and psychosis unravel her marriage to her husband (Robert Pattinson) and her grip on reality.
The supporting cast includes LaKeith Stanfield, Nick Nolte, and Sissy Spacek.
Die My Love had its world premiere at the 2025 Cannes Film Festival on
May 17, 2025, where it was nominated for the Palme d'Or.
It received generally positive reviews from critics,
with praise for Lawrence's performance.
At the 83rd Golden Globe Awards, Lawrence was nominated for
Best Actress in a Motion Picture – Drama.
It was theatrically released in the United States by Mubi on November 7, 2025.
The tone is emotional and intense.